

ASIEDU AMOAKO KWAME

Tel. No: +233 243364451

Email: akasiedu@gmail.com

#### PERSONAL DATA

Nationality Ghanaian

• Date of birth 23rd March, 1991

• Place of birth Bonwire, Ashanti Region

Marital Status SingleSex Male

#### **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

To effectively combine experiences in academia and on the job to analytically handle daily work related problems and see these problems as challenges and opportunities to progress towards the accomplishment of my goals in life and not as obstacles to development.

# **EXPERIENCE AND QUALITIES:**

- ✓ Highly experienced and innovative Supervisor with in-depth knowledge in Customer Service, Managerial Skills, Marketing, and Analytical skills.
- ✓ Ability to find identify problems and find technological solutions to such problems in a short time.
- ✓ Confident and a Team builder, able to motivate and communicate to achieve exceptional business results.
- ✓ Have the ability to work effectively and efficiently with or without supervision.
- ✓ A fast learner and ready to learn new things to gain more knowledge.
- ✓ Have a good interpersonal relationship.

- ✓ Good communication (verbal and written) skills.
- ✓ Good knowledge and skills in computing.

## **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND**

2009 –2013	BSc. Mathematics KNUST, Kumasi, Ghana
	(Second Class Upper Division)
2005 - 2008	Armed Forces Senior High School (W.A.S.S.C.E.) Kumasi, Ghana
2002 –2005	Station Basic School, Uaddara Barrack Kumasi (B.E.C.E).

## **PROFICIENCIES**

- 1. Microsoft Office Suite
  - i. Word
  - ii. Excel
  - iii. PowerPoint
- 2. Knowledgeable in statistical software packages
  - i. SPSS
  - ii. R-code
- 3. VBA
- 4. HTML
- 5. Matlab

### WORK EXPERIENCE

1. Institution: Clive—Ghana Limited

Description: Travel and Tour Company for Students Position: Co-founder and Chief Operations Officer

### **ROLES**

- i. Seeking for Travel sponsorship for Students
- ii. Preparing travel documents for students
- iii. Help students acquire passports

## 2. ATTACHMENT

Institution: Komfo Anokye Teaching Hospital (attachment)

Position: Biostatistician

Date: JUNE 2012 till AUGUST 2012

### **ROLES:**

i. Procuring consumables from hospital store.

- ii. Accounting and secretarial duties.
- iii. I developed an application to effective organize data and for data analysis

#### 3. NATIONAL SERVICE

Institution: Abesim Senior High School

Position: Teacher

Duration: September 2013 to August 2014

#### **ROLES:**

i. National Service representative for personnel in Abesim

ii. Mathematics and ICT teacher

iii. Organizing quizzes and field trips for students

iv. Member of Sports and Disciplinary committee

### 4. PART-TIME

Institution: Olistar Secondary Technical School

Position: Teacher

Duration: November 2013 to JULY 2014

## ROLES:

i. Mathematics and Integrated Science Teacher, Secondary Department

ii. Managing of school's database systems and maintenance of computers and accessories

iii. Disciplinary committee Chair-Person

## 5. PROJECT UNDETAKEN

- a. Thesis on the school feeding program as an indicator for higher enrolment and attendance in the basic schools
- b. A development of an application for data collection and analysis at the Physiotherapy Department (Komfo Anokye Teaching Hospital) Kumasi.

### EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES/POSITIONS HELD

- i. MEMBER: National Union of Anglican Students
  - Erecting canopies and arranging chairs for church activities
  - Setting up musical instruments
  - Past Financial Secretary (2007-2008)
- ii. Financial Secretary- Catholic and Anglican Students Union, Armed Forces Senior High School. 2006-2008
- iii. Execution Board Member- Chaplaincy Board, Armed Forces Senior High School. 2006-2008
- iv. Executive Member- Scripture Union (Armed Forces Senior High School 2006-2008)
- v. National Service representative for Abesim-Sunyani. (Service Year 2013/2014)

#### **INTEREST**

- Learning new programming languages
- Playing video games and "Facebooking"
- Socializing
- Cooking
- Playing the bass guitar and writing music
- Watching and playing football

# **REFERENCES**

- Mr. K.F Darkwah Head of Mathematics Department KNUST, Kumasi-Ghana
- Rev. Dr. William Obeng Denteh (Academic Supervisor)
  Lecturer, Mathematics Department, KNUST Kumasi
- Frank George Obeng Head of Abesim Senior High School, Abesim-Sunyani